4flick.com 2008-12-18

# Untitled Document

Intermark Media, Inc. (“Intermark”) has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering, use and dissemination practices solely for the web site located at www.intermarkmedia.com (the "Site") and its affiliated sites as noted herein. By using or accessing the Site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE.**

**Collection and Use of Personal Information  
** We do not collect personal information about Site users unless such information is voluntarily provided by the user. Our registration forms require consumers to provide certain contact information such as name and email address. This contact information is used and shared to facilitate the process of the service the consumer requests to send you promotional offers for various products and services via direct mail, telemarketing, SMS text messaging and email from third parties whom we work with that we feel may be of interest to you. Consumers who opt-in to receive offers or voluntarily provide their personal information to Intermark may receive email, telephone calls or direct mail from Intermark or our partners with whom we share personal information. If you do not want to receive offers from Intermark or its partners, you may opt-out of receiving future communications; see the Choice/Opt-Out section below. 

We may need to disclose personal information when required by law and when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us or to assist in the investigation of any potential fraud. We may also disclose personal information in connection with a sale, merger or reorganization of Intermark. 

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information  
**We may collect non-personal information (or aggregate information) during your use of our Site, including IP address, pages viewed, click-stream data and browsing habits. Non-personal information may be shared with third parties who are not affiliated with Intermark. 

Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your session and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use (and our third party advertisers may use) cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. We also use cookies once a form is submitted as an indicator that the application was filled and if you try to fill out another one within 60 days it will give you an option to either fill out another application or leave. "Cookies" are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web site. Many web sites use cookies for these purposes. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Site, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. Intermark does not use cookies to automatically retrieve personal information from your computer without your knowledge. 

In addition to cookies, we may also use (and our third party advertisers may use) clear gifs or web beacons to improve the performance of the Site, provide certain features such as advertising or to anonymously track usage of the Site. Clear gifs / web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, which operate much like a cookie, and are used to track the online activity of Site users. In addition, we may use such devices in our HTML-based emails to track the usage of such emails in much the same manner as usage of the Site is tracked. These devices are not used by Intermark to automatically collect person information. 

**Security  
** This Site has reasonable security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information under our control. We use SSL 128-bit encryption to transfer any personal information that you may submit in our application. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications will be free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers and your use of the Site demonstrates your assumption of this risk. 

**Choice/Opt-Out  
**To opt-out of any of a mailing from Intermark, you may follow the opt-out procedures set forth in our emails to you or send an email to us at [**optout@intermarkmedia.com**](mailto:optout@intermarkmedia.com). If you do not wish us to share your personal information with third parties who may use such information for direct marketing purposes, you may send an email to us at [**removepersonalinfo@intermarkmedia.com**](mailto:removepersonalinfo@intermarkmedia.com). 

However, we are not responsible for removing your personal information from the lists of any third party who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this policy. 

**Correct/Update  
** To change and modify information previously provided to Intermark, you may email us at [**update@intermarkmedia.com**](mailto:update@intermarkmedia.com). 

**Links**  
This Site contains links to other sites. Intermark is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. Please read the privacy policies of these linked sites, because their privacy practices may differ from ours. 

**Protection for Children  
** We have no intention of collecting personal information from children under the age of 13. When we become aware that personal information from a child under 13 has been collected without such child’s parent or guardian’s consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy  
**We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. However, if at any time in the future we plan to use personal information in a way that differs from this policy, we will post such changes here and provide you the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes. 

**Legal Statement  
**Use of this Site is governed by, and subject to, the legal notices contained in our Legal Statement. Your use, or access, of the Site constitutes your agreement to be bound by these provisions. **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE.**

**USA  
** Our Site is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Site, you authorize the export of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy. 

**Effective Date  
**This privacy policy is effective and was last updated on August 30, 2005. 

**Contacting Intermark  
** If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact:
